本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
我们到了  这就是暑圣节百货
Here we are. The Summerween Superstore.
等等  暑什么
Wait-- summer what?
暑圣节
Summerween!
怪诞小镇里的人都很喜欢万圣节
The people of this town love Halloween so much,
所以大家每年都会过两次
They celebrate it twice a year.
你不知道吧  暑圣节就在今天
And wouldn't you know it? It's today!
你总是随身带着这个日历吗
Do you always carry that calendar in your pocket?
没错
Yes.
暑圣节  听起来不太自然啊
Summerween? Something about this feels unnatural.
有免费的糖果领哦
There's free candy!
赶快到服饰区域去
To the costume aisle!
我真的很想借你一只手用用  不过我貌似没有
I'd lend you a hand-- but I don't seem to have any!
（注：lend a hand有帮助之意）
它倒是说了实话
This guy tells it like it is.
先生
Sir.
请不要按了
Could please stop pushing that.
女士  如果你能让它们看起来不那么搞笑的话
Ma'am, make these heads less hilarious
我就答应你
And you got yourself a deal.
随你便吧
well!
今晚那些小屁孩到访我家时
When the children come to my door tonight,
肯定会惊叫着逃跑的
They're gonna run away screaming
这都是恐惧之神斯坦·派恩斯的功劳
from Stan Pines, master of fright!
砰
Boo!
糟糕  貌似这一桶漏了
Uh-oh. Think this one's leaking!
请把警察叫过来并把派恩斯一家清出去
Have the police come and eject the Pines family from the store.
-今天不行  -我的眼睛
- Not today! - My eyes!
你已经付钱了吧
You paid for this stuff, right?
那当然
Of course!
斯坦元
活生生的钱
我讨厌暑圣节
I hate Summerween.
咱们走吧
Let's move!
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
翻译： mango
校订： line  WaitinZ
■
后期： line  WaitinZ  liloelva
怪诞小镇  第一季第十二集
Gravity Falls  S01E12  Summerween
真是激动人心啊
I am so excited!
我们一定要穿上最吓人的服饰  还要拿到最多的糖果
We're gonna have the best costumes, get the most candy...
还要让自己吃撑
And have the biggest stomachaches ever!
我从来都没有看到你们这么激动过
Dude, I've never seen you guys so pumped.
在被拐到这里之前  我和迪普都
Well, back at home, me and Dipper were
是“不给糖就捣蛋”之王
kind of the kings of trick-or-treating.
我们是穿着奇异服装的双胞胎  吃掉一切的僵尸
Twins in costumes-- the people eat it up.
那你们在这儿就最好小心点咯
Well, you dudes better be careful out there.
夜晚是食尸鬼和妖精的天堂
It's a night of ghouls and goblins,
更不要说
Not to mention...
暑圣节之灵了
The Summerween trickster.
暑圣节什么
The Summerween what what?
幽灵挨家挨户拜访
The trickster goes door to door.
传说凡是没有暑圣节精神的孩子
So the legend goes, eating children
都会被吃掉
who lack the Summerween spirit.
你不用担心我们
Well, you don't have to worry about us.
我们可是很有暑圣节精神的
We've got spirit to go around.
天  这些是什么啊
Oh, what is this stuff?
我都没听说过这些牌子
I've never even heard of these brands.
凳子小软糖
Gummy chairs?
沙滩棒棒糖
Sand pop?
满足先生巧克力
Mr. Adequate bar?
这些糖都是傻瓜才买的地摊货
This is all cheapo loser candy!
别在这儿宣泄不满了  孩子们
Quiet your discontent, children,
免得让暑圣节之灵听到了
Lest the trickster overhear.
苏斯  你的斗篷被夹到裤衩里面了
Your cape is caught in your fly, soos.
说得对
Touché.
再见了  地摊货
Goodbye, loser candy!
不给糖就捣蛋的孩子来了
Trick-or-treaters!
赶快把那些恶心的糖果给他们
Quick, give 'em that terrible candy!
暑圣节快
Happy summer--
-什么  - 咋啦  小松鼠
- Wha--?! - 'Sup, squirt?
嘿  迪普
Hey, Dipper.
温蒂吗  哈哈
Wendy! Ha ha ha!
你们过来有事吗
Ow! Wh-- what's up, guys?
我又把我的夹克衫漏这儿了
Ugh! I left my jacket here, again.
那些糖果是用来干什么的
Hey, what's with the candy?
你要去登门讨糖吗
You goin' trick- or-treating or something?
我实际上
Well, actually, I, uh...
别说了  罗比  他才不会去呢
Shut up, Robbie. Of course he's not going trick-or-treating.
是不会
No, yeah, uh...
只有那些小朋友才会做这个
Trick-or-treating is for babies...
可能是吧
I guess.
你要不要也来参加我们的派对
You should come to this party with us.
谭布丽的爸妈都出去了
Tambry's parents are out of town,
大家都自由了
And it's gonna be off the chain!
对于你没有得到消息我一点都不觉得奇怪
Not surprised you didn't hear about it.
谭布丽暑圣节晚会
嘿  等等
Hey, guys, wait!
我也可能会去参加的
Maybe I'll see you at the party.
如果你没把时间花到过家家上的话
If you're not too busy playing dress-up.
九点钟准时开始  别忘了哦
It's at nine! Don't forget!
我要怎么跟梅宝解释呢
What am I gonna tell Mabel?
斯坦叔公  这些都是我的好朋友
Gruncle Stan, these are my best friends...
- 这是糖糖和格兰达  - 我甜蜜地都可以把自己吃掉
- Candy and Grenda! - I am so sweet, I could eat myself.
您好  派恩斯先生
Hello, Mr. Pines.
你感冒了吗
You got a cold, honey?
你的声音听起来好奇怪
Something wrong with your voice there?
你什么意思  为什么你会这么说
What do you mean? Why would you say that?
摇摇要跟我们一起来吗
Is Waddles coming with us?
我也想让他去  但是
I wish he could, but...
他有些重要的事情要做
He's got some very important meetings to attend!
将这些文档放入I区域
File these documents under "I,"
并记录  我有一条卷曲的尾巴
For "I have a curly tail!"
你的哥哥呢
What about your brother?
你们就等着看迪普的服装吧
Oh, man, guys, just wait until you see Dipper's costume.
那真是太棒了
It's amazing!
他来了
Here he comes now.
这的确是很适合迪普穿的服装
That is a very good Dipper costume.
搞什么啊  哥哥  你的服装呢
What the hey-hey, bro-bro? Where's your costume?
我不能去参加你们的讨糖活动了
Look, I can't go trick-or-treating.
我现在病得很厉害
I'm, uh, really sick.
可能是那些劣质糖果弄的  你们自己去吧
Must have been that bad candy. You go on without me.
要坚强起来  你的暑圣节精神呢
Fight through it, man! Where's your Summerween spirit?
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick or treat.
喂  真的吗
Dude, really?
你的年龄可能不适合这个游戏了  很抱歉
You're a little old for this, man. Sorry.
等等  我是
But wait. I'm...!
-你为什么要关门啊  -我告诉你了  梅宝
Why'd you close the door? I told you, Mabel...
今晚我不在状态上
I'm just not feeling it tonight.
我想玩一会“不给糖就捣蛋”游戏会让你找到状态的
I think a little trick-or-treating will make you feel better.
我不想玩这个
I'm not trick-or-treating.
哥们儿  你去讨下一家的糖吧
Look, man, just go to another house!
迪普  你的友好暑圣待客态度又到哪里去了
Dipper, where's your summerween hospitality?
我不明白
I'm not getting that.
我明白
Well, I am.
我代我的哥哥说抱歉
I apologize for my brother.
那些软糖让他根本就没有兴趣玩游戏
He came down with a case of the grumpy grumps.
闭嘴
Silence!
你们侮辱了我  你们要为此付出
You have insulted me, and for this you must pay...
你们的生命
With your lives!
哇  这面罩真可爱
Ohh! What a cute little mask.
你真好玩  不是吗
You're a funny guy, aren't you?
我好玩吗
Funny am I?
不给糖就捣蛋
"Twick-or-tweat"!
我的名字是格尼
My name is Gorney!
啊  请记住我
Aah! Remember me!
格尼
Gorney!
让他逃避这个命运的唯一方法是
There's only one way for you to avoid his fate--
我要被好好款待
I need treat.
如果你能在最后一盏西瓜灯
If you can collect 500 pieces of candy
熄灭之前讨到五百颗糖
And bring it to me before the last
并把它们带给我的话
Jack-o'-melon goes out...
我可以让你们活下去
I will let you live.
一个晚上收集五百颗糖  这不可能啊
Five hundred treats in one night? That's impossible!
选择在于你  小孩
The choice is yours, children.
你要不去讨糖果
You must trick-or-treat...
要不就死
Or die!
我的天啊  梅宝  知道这意味着什么吗
Oh, my gosh, Mabel, do you know what this means?
我明白
I do.
这意味着你要去跟我们一起“不给糖就捣蛋”了
It means you have to come trick-or-treating!
那家伙是谁啊
Who was that guy?
是苏斯告诉我们的传说中的那个人
It's the legend Soos told us about.
竟然是真的
It's true!
我们该怎么办  该怎么办
What do we do, what do we do?
发生什么了
What's going on out here, dudes?
我听到了骚动
I heard a ruckus.
骚动  这词真好玩
That's a funny word-- "Ruckus."
苏斯  有个怪物要让我们去登门讨糖
Soos, a monster is making us trick-or-treat,
否则他会把我们吃掉的
or else he's gonna eat us.
我拍了张照片
I got a picture.
暑圣节之灵
The Summerween trickster!
我的天啊  你们有大麻烦了
Oh, man, dude, you guys are in crazy bonkers trouble.
我们怎样才能在一个晚上讨到这么多的糖呢
How are we gonna get that much candy in one night?
不可能的
There's no way!
大家听好了
Listen up, people!
有些人可能会觉得被一个嗜血的
Now, some might say that being cursed
节日怪兽诅咒绝对不是好事情
by a bloodthirsty holiday monster is a bad thing...
我都冒冷汗了
I wet myself!
不过那怪兽找错对象了
But that monster messed with the wrong crew.
我们很有糖糖的意志  有格兰达的力量
With Candy's spirit, Grenda's strength,
迪普的才智  还有
Dipper's brains, and...
苏斯  在这儿
Soos, here...
我们会开心地讨到五百颗糖果的
We'll get 500 pieces of candy and have fun doing it, too,
就算要花一整晚也没关系
Even if it takes all night!
赶快到街道上去吧
To the streets!
一整晚
All night?
但是不要忘了我还病着呢
But-- but I'm sick, remember?
迪普  想想哪个更糟糕
Dipper, what's worse--
是被恐怖的怪兽吃掉呢
Getting eaten by a horrifying monster,
还是跟我们去登门讨糖果呢
Or going trick-or-treating with us?
来吧
Come on!
啊  暑圣节
Ah, Summerween!
那些小屁孩们绝对不会料想到这个的
Those kids aren't gonna know what hit 'em!
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick-or-treat!
我能帮到你们什
what can I do for--!
哎呀  不要
Oh Oh no No.
能给糖了吗
Can we have candy now?
你们竟然没有被吓倒
What's the matter with you kids?
这恐怕是你们这么大以来看到的最恐怖的东西了吧
That was the scariest thing you've ever seen, right?
你看过这个吗
Well, have you seen... This?
内脏啊  如假包换的内脏啊
Guts! Very real guts!
呃  我们貌似两岁就
Uh... We've been watching horror movies
开始看恐怖电影了
since we were, like, two years old.
没错  我们很难被吓倒的
Yeah, we're not scared.
你会的
Oh, you will be.
You will be.
为了荣耀  孩子们  冲啊
For glory, my children! Charge!
你让我表现得不错
You make a great me.
不  是你让我表现得不错
No, you make a great me!
不  是你  呵呵
No, you do! Heh heh!
我不明白为什么我们不
I don't understand why we
直接把糖果买齐然后就结束走人
can't just buy our candy and be done with it.
这样就没有“讨不到糖就去死”的乐趣了
That sort of takes the fun out of "Trick-or-treat or die."
我很想把“死”字从这句话里拿出来
I'm trying to take the "Die" Out of "Trick-or-treat or die."
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick-or-treat!
你们真是可爱啊
Well, aren't you just the cutest!
大家都穿了服装吗
And is everyone in costume?
哦  不错
Oh, good!
- 真不错  - 暑圣节快乐
- Wonderful! - Happy Summerween!
不给糖就捣蛋
Trick-or-treat!
大家都穿了服装吗
And is everybody in costume?
扫烟囱的  肥象男
Chimney sweep, elephant man,
橡皮清洁刷  蚂蚁农场
Squeegee, ant farm.
那你扮演的是什么
Oh, and what are you supposed to be?
实际上  我什么都没有扮
Uh, actually, I'm not dressed up as anything.
我们现在很赶时间
We-- we're kind of in a hurry here.
哦  我明白了
Oh. I see.
好好享受吧
Enjoy!
一片黑甘草精
One piece of black licorice?
马戏花生  这些都是失败者才吃的
Circus peanut! This is loser candy!
才四块糖果
Four pieces of candy?
这什么时候才是个头啊
This is gonna take forever.
迪普  我们得加油了
We've gotta up our game, Dipper.
你要赶快把你的服装穿上
You gotta put on your costume.
都告诉你了  梅宝  我根本就不在状态上
I told you, I'm not up to it, Mabel.
真的吗
Oh, really?
我看到过比这些更好的
I've seen better.
时间在流逝哦
Tick tock.
还在因为生病而不想穿服装吗
So, what was that about being too sick to wear a costume?
我们要糖  我们要糖
We want candy! We want candy!
好吧  我服了  孩子们
All right, you got me, kids.
你们赢了
You guys win.
我猜我也不是很恐怖吧
I guess I'm not that scary, you know?
你们已经  你们  哎
You've-- you-- oh, no!
为什么  为什么有一头猪从我的胸膛里出来了
Why? Why is there a pig jumping out of my chest?
-糖果 -赶快给糖果
- Candy. - Can-dee!
怎么才能吓倒你们两个怪胎呢
What scares you two freaks?
来  看看这个
Here, watch this.
什么  这是什么  是一只
What? What is this, some kind of--
是一只猫或者是
Some kind of kitten or...?
你到底怎么了  斯坦·派恩斯
What happened to you, Stan Pines?
到底怎么了
What happened?
让我首次向大众宣布
Introducing, for the first time in public...
花生酱果冻装
Tah-dah! Peanut butter and jelly!
我会让你在网上迅速出名的
I will make you internet-famous!
嘿  赶快删了
Hey, erase that.
咱们赶快把事情做完吧
Let's just get this over with, okay?
做完  做完
Over with! Over with!
你觉得这和之前有区别吗
Do you really think this will make a difference?
我们是双胞胎哦
Twins!
赶快去拿糖果吧
Let's get that candy, guys!
三十四  三十五
Thirty-four... Thirty-five...
三十六
Thirty-six.
看到了吗  因为  我懂了
You see? Because... Yeah, I get it.
二十二  二十三  二十四
Twenty-two, twenty-three, twenty-four...
一共一百二十四颗
A hundred and twenty-four!
赶快啊  继续加油
Come on, come on!
你好
Hello!
哇  这面具真恐怖
what a horrible mask!
这就是我的脸
That's just my face.
这才是面具
This is a mask!
这样看起来反而更好
It's actually better.
四百九十八  四百九十九
Four ninety-eight, four ninety-nine!
我们做到了
We did it!
再来一颗就胜利啦
All we need is one more piece of candy.
现在只是八点半而已  看起来我们速度不错
And it's only 8:30. Perfect timing!
没错  而且你的病完全好了
Yeah, and your cough went away, too!
我现在就在附近逛逛  顺便把货车开过来
Dude, I'm gonna go around and grab the truck.
苏斯走啦
Soos away!
我诅咒最后一个冲到目标屋子的人会长蜡嘴唇
Last one to the final house is a pair of wax lips!
不是我  不要
Not me! No!
现在就是去温蒂的派对的好时间啦
The perfect time to go to Wendy's party,
不会有人知道我讨了糖果玩的
And no one needs to know I was trick-or-treating.
嘿  迪普
Hey, Dipper!
嘿  温蒂
Oh, hey, Wendy.
怎么样啦
What's up?
你会来参加聚会吗
Are you coming to the party?
你在这里干什么
What are you doin' out here?
呃  我在去那儿的路上
Oh, I'm-- I'm on my way.
我挺喜欢看这些小孩子讨糖果的
I like watching the trick-or-treaters.
这勾起了我儿时的回忆
Reminds me of when I was a kid.
好吧  你会来的吧
Okay, then. You're coming, right?
当然  当然
Definitely, definitely.
不错  派对见
Cool. See ya there.
一会见
Later, guys.
你原来真正想去的是那个派对
You're going to a party.
好吧  嘿  我
Well-- well, hey, I-- aah!
原来这就是你看起来这么奇怪
That's why you were acting so weird
而且还不断地催促我们的原因
And trying to hurry us.
你根本就没生病
You're not sick at all,
所以说如果那个疯怪兽没出现的话
So if it wasn't for this crazy monster,
你会直接在我们最喜欢的
You were gonna ditch me...
节日中抛弃我的
On our favorite holiday!
那个热爱万圣节的迪普到哪里去了
What happened to the Dipper who used love Halloween?
那些糖呢
And where's all the candy?
别担心
Relax, relax.
我把它放在这儿了  就在这群灌木后面
I left it right here, behind this bush.
糟糕
Oh, no!
-你到底做了什么  -我  我
- What did you do? - Well, I-- I--!
呃  大家注意一下
Uh... Guys?
糟糕了
Oh, no!
所有的西瓜灯笼都熄灭了
All the jack-o'-melons are out!
快看
Look!
晚安啦
Good night!
-不要  -什么
- Stop! - What?
不  不  千万不要
No, no, no, no, no! Don't, don't, don't!
发生什么了
Huh? What's happening?
不要把蜡烛吹灭就是了
Just don't blow out that candle.
我听不到你说话
What?!
别吹灭这个蜡烛
Don't blow out that candle!
我可是麦戈科特老人家呢
I'm old man McGucket!
等等
Wait!
对不起
Sorry!
唔  好险
Whoo, that was close.
你们好啊
Knock-knock.
好了孩子们  我的糖呢
So children. Where's my candy?..
我发誓我们讨到过五百颗糖的
I swear, we had all 500 pieces!
看  就在下面的某个地方
Look, it's down there somewhere.
我们还能把它们捡回来呢
We can still get it.
现在恐怕已经太晚了
I'm afraid it's too late!
你错过了你最后一次将功补过的机会
That was your last chance.
大家赶快跑
Go! Go, go, go!
-啊  迪普  -梅宝
- Aah! Dipper! - Mabel!
我们活下来了  耶
We're alive! Yeah!
- 好险  - 苏斯
- Whoa! - Soos!
那貌似不是一个普通的行人呢
That wasn't, like, a regular pedestrian, was it?
是那个大怪兽啊
It was the monster.
谢谢你  苏斯
Thanks, Soos.
我只是很高兴这事情结束了
I'm just glad it's over.
不是吗
Right?
大家戴好安全带了吗
Did everyone remember to put on their seatbelts?
都戴好啦
Yes. Yes. Yes.
咱们出发吧
Let's go.
嘿  你还好吗
Hey, are you okay?
小屋里面应该有创可贴
There are probably some bandages back at the shack.
各位
Guys?
赶快刹车
Brakes, brakes, brakes!
我们得藏起来
We have to hide!
唯一的出口被它挡住了
It's blocking the only exit.
大家保持安静
Everyone stay quiet.
哦  现在你倒是开始担心这个怪兽了
Oh, now you're worried about the monster!
我还以为你心中只想着温蒂呢
I thought all you cared about was Wendy.
梅宝  你知道那不是真的
Mabel, you know that's not true.
我只是  感觉我的年龄已经不适合
I just-- I felt like I was getting a little too old
玩万圣节讨糖游戏了
to go trick-or-treating.
所以我们才要好好享受啊  迪普
That's exactly why we need to go trick-or-treating, Dipper.
我们正在逐渐地长大
We're getting older.
已经不剩多少我们能欢乐玩耍的万圣节了
There's not that many Halloweens left.
我也从没有意识到这会是我们的最后一个万圣节
I guess I didn't realize it was already our last one.
-我们得想办法逃出去  -如果它发现我们怎么办
- We have to escape. - What if it sees us?
我们只能找点什么东西
If only there was something we could use to cover
来掩盖我们的身体和脸
Our bodies and faces with--
你知道的  像某种伪装那样
You know, like a disguise of some kind.
这边走
This way!
马上就到了
Almost there!
苏斯
Soos!
别
Stop!
苏斯  你千万别动
Soos, don't you dare!
对不起  今天我的压力真是太大了
Sorry, dude, today's been way stressful.
我得找点乐子
I need some levity.
真好  它们都没电了
Oh, thank goodness. It was out of batteries.
苏斯  不要
Soos! No!
不管怎么样  我都是一个骷髅头
No matter the score, I'm always "A head"!
这个咯咯叫的骷髅头代表了一个时代的声音
this cackling head's the voice of a generation.
什么
Wha--?
嘿  老怪
Hey, monster!
盐水太妃糖  真是恶心死了
Salt water taffy? Gross!
你是什么  等等  不就是吗
What are you--? Wait, it is!
你还没想明白吗
You really haven't figured it out yet?
你不认得我吗  看着我的脸
Don't you recognize me? Look at my face.
再看得近一点
Look closely.
那些傻蛋才买的糖果
Loser candy!
没错  你有没有停下来想过
That's right. Did you ever stop and think
无人喜欢的
About the candy at the bottom of the bag
袋子最底下里的那些糖
That no one likes?
每年重力泉的小孩子都会
Every year, the children of Gravity Falls
把不要的糖果都扔到垃圾堆去
throw away all of the rejected candy into the dump.
所以我回来复仇了
So I seek revenge--
报复那些对我拒之不理的小孩子们
Revenge on the picky children who cast me aside.
我是由每片被扔掉的黑甘草片
I'm made of every tossed piece of black licorice,
每条被遗弃的巧克力
every discarded bar of old chocolate
还有像面粉一样的东西做成的
with, like, that white powder stuff on it.
你知道那是什么吗
You know that stuff?
我最讨厌那东西了
I hate that stuff!
没有人会喜欢吃我的
No one would eat me!
但现在我要把你们吃掉
But now, I'm going to eat you!
我要把你给  哦
I'm gonna eat... Ohh!
那是什么
What is that?
怎么了  老兄
'sup, bro?
伙计们  你们想来点这个吗
Mm. Dudes, you want some of this?
等等  你竟然觉得我味道不错
Wait. You actually think I taste good?
呃  是的  你知道的
Uh, sure. You know.
我这辈子等的就是这句话了
All I've ever wanted is for someone to say that I was good.
我真的很开心
I'm so happy!
这哭得有点诡异  但是
The crying makes it a little weird, but...
我还是继续吃吧
I guess I'm still eating.
你好啊  格尼
'Sup, Gorney?
我受伤啦
I've been "Twaumatized"!
-现在怎么办  -我们去要我们的糖果吧
- Now what?  - Let's get our candy already.
老家伙  老家伙
Old dude! Old dude!
斯坦  洗个澡吧  洗去这份奇耻大辱
Wash off the shame, Stan, wash off the shame.
哈  他竟然以为他吓得到我们
Ha! He thought he could scare us!
呃  怎么了
Heh? What's that?
还是成功了
Still got it.
-嘿斯坦  -斯坦叔公好
- Hey, Stan. - Hi, Gruncle Stan.
你好  派恩斯先生
Hello, Mr. Pines.
玩的怎么样  嘿  迪普
How's it hangin'? Hey, Dipper.
温蒂  我没在派对上见到你  你去哪儿了
Wendy! I didn't see you at the party. Where where you?
呃  我
Uh, I, uh...
我和我的妹妹去
I was trick-or-treating...
玩“不给糖就捣蛋了”
With my sister.
没错
Yeah.
嗯  反正那派对差极了
Mm. Party was lame, anyway.
罗比把棒棒糖棍吞进肚了  现在他得回家养病了
Robbie ate a lollipop stick first and had to go home sick.
哎呀  真糟糕
Aw, man.
我们家家户户地去讨糖
We went to every single house,
到头来自己一颗都没吃到
And we didn't even get to eat any candy!
吃糖吗
Candy?
这些糖怎么样
How's that for candy!
现在让我们继续收看《恐怖镇来的可怕人》
And now back to the Fear Guy From Terror Town Street!
知道吗  孩子们  我一直在想
You know, kids, I been thinking--
今天已经要结束了  我发现暑圣节的真正意义
At the end of the day, Summerween isn't about candy,
不在于糖果  服装  或者是可怕的人
or costumes, or even scary people.
其实在于一个家庭能欢聚一堂
It's a day when the whole family can get together at one place
赞美真正重要的东西
and celebrate what really matters--
纯粹的邪恶
Pure evil.
今晚我吃掉了一个活生生的人
I ate a man alive tonight.
哼哼
你被解雇了
每天朝九晚五只为了营生
Working nine to five what a way to make a living
我讨厌星期一
勉强支撑  他们只是索取  从不给予
Barely getting by it's all taking and no giving
这个饼图我吃了
梅维斯  请帮我
拿一下电话
谢谢
他们窃取你的好主意  从不把功劳算在你头上
They just use your mind and they never give you credit
要给我升职吗
没给我升职
如果你每天工作八小时只是全身心地干活的话
It's enough to drive you crazy if you let it
平淡无奇的星期五
你真的能被逼疯
Nine to five for service and devotion
累晕了